export const Data = [
  {
      question: "What is the recommended minimum age for a child to start using a forward-facing car seat?",
      optionA: "1 year",
      optionB: "2 years",
      optionC: "3 years",
      optionD: "4 years",
      answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a common household item that should be kept out of reach to prevent accidental poisoning in children?",
    optionA: "Fruit juice",
    optionB: "Cleaning supplies",
    optionC: "Teddy bear",
    optionD: "Cereal",
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "At what age can children usually begin to safely use a bicycle helmet?",
    optionA: "2 years",
    optionB: "5 years",
    optionC: "8 years",
    optionD: "10 years",
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "To reduce the risk of Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (SIDS), babies should be placed to sleep on their",
    optionA: "Stomach",
    optionB: "Chest",
    optionC: "Side",
    optionD: "Back",
    answer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "When cooking, which of these precautions should be taken to ensure child safety?",
    optionA: "Leave sharp knives within reach",
    optionB: "Use small appliances near water",
    optionC: "Keep pot handles facing outward",
    optionD: "Place hot pots on low tables",
    answer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "To prevent choking, what size should objects or toys given to young children be?",
    optionA: "Small enough to fit in their mouth",
    optionB: "Large enough to cover their face",
    optionC: "Small enough to fit in their hand",
    optionD: "Large enough to hold with both hands",
    answer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "What's the recommended temperature for bathwater when bathing a child?",
    optionA: "90°F (32°C)",
    optionB: "100°F (38°C)",
    optionC: "110°F (43°C)",
    optionD: "120°F (49°C)",
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is an appropriate way to childproof electrical outlets?",
    optionA: "Use scotch tape to cover outlets",
    optionB: "Insert plastic forks into outlets",
    optionC: "Install outlet covers or caps",
    optionD: "Paint over the outlets",
    answer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "When using a high chair, what safety measure should be taken to prevent falls?",
    optionA: "Remove the safety straps",
    optionB: "Place the chair near the edge of a table",
    optionC: "Leave the child unattended",
    optionD: "Buckle the child with safety straps",
    answer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "To avoid burns, what's a good practice when serving hot beverages around children?",
    optionA: "Use glass cups",
    optionB: "Serve beverages at room temperature",
    optionC: "Allow children to hold the cup themselves",
    optionD: "Keep hot beverages out of reach",
    answer: "d"
  }
]